[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "When that happens a business like yours tends to do well?", "question_tokens": ["When", "that", "happens", "a", "business", "like", "yours", "tends", "to", "do", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "That's sort of a misnomer.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "sort", "of", "a", "misnomer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "People still want to sell then you can get rid of it?", "question_tokens": ["People", "still", "want", "to", "sell", "then", "you", "can", "get", "rid", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "I mean who comes in your store?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "who", "comes", "in", "your", "store", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "I mean it's everybody, especially our store.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "'s", "everybody", ",", "especially", "our", "store", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "JJS", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Why the billionaire come to a pawnshop?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "the", "billionaire", "come", "to", "a", "pawnshop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "People don't realize, most billionaires actually pretty cheap.", "answer_tokens": ["People", "do", "n't", "realize", ",", "most", "billionaires", "actually", "pretty", "cheap", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "I know there must be a lot of surprises, but when you look back what have been the moments, you go, wow, when somebody brought something in that's really knocked your socks off?", "question_tokens": ["I", "know", "there", "must", "be", "a", "lot", "of", "surprises", ",", "but", "when", "you", "look", "back", "what", "have", "been", "the", "moments", ",", "you", "go", ",", "wow", ",", "when", "somebody", "brought", "something", "in", "that", "'s", "really", "knocked", "your", "socks", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "That happens actually a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "happens", "actually", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "This is actually the battle plan for Iwo Jima, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "actually", "the", "battle", "plan", "for", "Iwo", "Jima", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iwo Jima"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Who brought this in?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "brought", "this", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "It was a person who's father had been on Iwo Jima.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "person", "who", "'s", "father", "had", "been", "on", "Iwo", "Jima", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "How did you assess the value?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "assess", "the", "value", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, this was a few years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "was", "a", "few", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$3500"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "$", "CD", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "But do you remember even the ballpark?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "remember", "even", "the", "ballpark", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "I think it was right around $3500, something like that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "right", "around", "$", "3500", ",", "something", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$8,000"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "So eight grand, it's coming off the wall, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "eight", "grand", ",", "it", "'s", "coming", "off", "the", "wall", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "$8,000 or an Iwo Jima plan, I'll take the eight grand.", "answer_tokens": ["$", "8,000", "or", "an", "Iwo", "Jima", "plan", ",", "I", "'ll", "take", "the", "eight", "grand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2000"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "So do you remember his story?", "question_tokens": ["So", "do", "you", "remember", "his", "story", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Yes, I think his story was basically that he -- you know, he got injured, wasn't able to compete in 2000 and was doing some other things.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "his", "story", "was", "basically", "that", "he", "--", "you", "know", ",", "he", "got", "injured", ",", "was", "n't", "able", "to", "compete", "in", "2000", "and", "was", "doing", "some", "other", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "How do you quantify an Olympic medal?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "quantify", "an", "Olympic", "medal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "That's a very difficult thing because they rarely if ever get on the market.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "very", "difficult", "thing", "because", "they", "rarely", "if", "ever", "get", "on", "the", "market", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "So what -- do you remember what you paid him for it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "--", "do", "you", "remember", "what", "you", "paid", "him", "for", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "So he'll never get them back?", "question_tokens": ["So", "he", "'ll", "never", "get", "them", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Sad, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Sad", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "It's sad.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "sad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "-- is the lesson you handed down to your son, you can't afford to get emotionally involved?", "question_tokens": ["--", "is", "the", "lesson", "you", "handed", "down", "to", "your", "son", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "afford", "to", "get", "emotionally", "involved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "One of the things is a pawn broker with a heart is usually a pawn broker out of business.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "things", "is", "a", "pawn", "broker", "with", "a", "heart", "is", "usually", "a", "pawn", "broker", "out", "of", "business", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Is there anything you would turn down?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "you", "would", "turn", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Have you ever turned anything down?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "turned", "anything", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "We won't take any German World War II items.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "wo", "n't", "take", "any", "German", "World", "War", "II", "items", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "You know, I won't do it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "wo", "n't", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Is there any other sort of thing you just feel strongly you wouldn't want to be party to?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "other", "sort", "of", "thing", "you", "just", "feel", "strongly", "you", "would", "n't", "want", "to", "be", "party", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I mean just anything in that area.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "just", "anything", "in", "that", "area", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "And I suppose the obvious question, what is the most expensive thing you've ever bought?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "suppose", "the", "obvious", "question", ",", "what", "is", "the", "most", "expensive", "thing", "you", "'ve", "ever", "bought", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "It's a real easy one.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "real", "easy", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "So do people actually walk in with gold bars?", "question_tokens": ["So", "do", "people", "actually", "walk", "in", "with", "gold", "bars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Oh, yes, every day.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What's the biggest -- what's the biggest chunk of gold you've ever had to deal with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "biggest", "--", "what", "'s", "the", "biggest", "chunk", "of", "gold", "you", "'ve", "ever", "had", "to", "deal", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "I can't remember what it was, I just remember we gave him 500 grand for it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "remember", "what", "it", "was", ",", "I", "just", "remember", "we", "gave", "him", "500", "grand", "for", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "$500,000?", "question_tokens": ["$", "500,000", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$500,000"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "And what is the -- if you're smart what is the markup if you move quickly on something like that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "the", "--", "if", "you", "'re", "smart", "what", "is", "the", "markup", "if", "you", "move", "quickly", "on", "something", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Actually, in our shop, it's weird.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "in", "our", "shop", ",", "it", "'s", "weird", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "On that kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["On", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I mean, it's a lot of people I don't understand who are in business will say, I'll never do that for 1 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "I", "do", "n't", "understand", "who", "are", "in", "business", "will", "say", ",", "I", "'ll", "never", "do", "that", "for", "1", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "And is that -- is that the attitude and strategy really?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "that", "--", "is", "that", "the", "attitude", "and", "strategy", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Take the cash when you can?", "question_tokens": ["Take", "the", "cash", "when", "you", "can", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Yes, I mean, you have to -- I mean, it's business.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "have", "to", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "business", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "The worst thing for you is a fully stocked store presumably?", "question_tokens": ["The", "worst", "thing", "for", "you", "is", "a", "fully", "stocked", "store", "presumably", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "It's a tough struggle, you know, I mean, because you're always wanting to buy stuff, you know it's tough to sell the stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "tough", "struggle", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "because", "you", "'re", "always", "wanting", "to", "buy", "stuff", ",", "you", "know", "it", "'s", "tough", "to", "sell", "the", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "I have a few dodge -- I mean, I -- here's my BlackBerry, I mean, given that it's been owned by me, is it worth more or less than if it hadn't been owned by me?", "question_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "few", "dodge", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "--", "here", "'s", "my", "BlackBerry", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "given", "that", "it", "'s", "been", "owned", "by", "me", ",", "is", "it", "worth", "more", "or", "less", "than", "if", "it", "had", "n't", "been", "owned", "by", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "I think it would be worth a little bit more on you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "would", "be", "worth", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "on", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "What kind of markup?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "markup", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "God, it is a BlackBerry.", "answer_tokens": ["God", ",", "it", "is", "a", "BlackBerry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "What do you say to them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "I mean surely your natural leaning would be toward the guy that believes the same that you do?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "surely", "your", "natural", "leaning", "would", "be", "toward", "the", "guy", "that", "believes", "the", "same", "that", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "I think you're right in that -- in that instant.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "'re", "right", "in", "that", "--", "in", "that", "instant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Who's more charismatic to you?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "more", "charismatic", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I think they're both -- I think they're both amazing men.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'re", "both", "--", "I", "think", "they", "'re", "both", "amazing", "men", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Will you be voting?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "be", "voting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "I will definitely be voting.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "definitely", "be", "voting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What are you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, here's the thing, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "here", "'s", "the", "thing", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Do you think it's wrong in modern-day America that someone like Mitt Romney, who's made hundreds of millions of dollars and, you know, probably not quite as much as you have, Joel, but he's done OK for himself, but -- that he gets lambasted for his success, lambasted for making that money, that somehow it's become a bad thing to be rich and successful in America?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "wrong", "in", "modern-day", "America", "that", "someone", "like", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "who", "'s", "made", "hundreds", "of", "millions", "of", "dollars", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "probably", "not", "quite", "as", "much", "as", "you", "have", ",", "Joel", ",", "but", "he", "'s", "done", "OK", "for", "himself", ",", "but", "--", "that", "he", "gets", "lambasted", "for", "his", "success", ",", "lambasted", "for", "making", "that", "money", ",", "that", "somehow", "it", "'s", "become", "a", "bad", "thing", "to", "be", "rich", "and", "successful", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["millions of dollars"], "LOCATION": ["America", "America"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Joel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "You must feel offended when you hear him say something like that, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "feel", "offended", "when", "you", "hear", "him", "say", "something", "like", "that", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well, Piers, I'm -- here I go again, but I'm for mercy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "'m", "--", "here", "I", "go", "again", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "for", "mercy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "How many books have you done?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "books", "have", "you", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I've done four.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "done", "four", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "And how many tens of millions of copies have you sold?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "many", "tens", "of", "millions", "of", "copies", "have", "you", "sold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "How do you convince them to take your lead?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "convince", "them", "to", "take", "your", "lead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Well, I think that's hope the big part of the ministry is that, you know, and we face difficulties, too.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "hope", "the", "big", "part", "of", "the", "ministry", "is", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "and", "we", "face", "difficulties", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Did you worry about dipping your toe there into a very hot political situation?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "worry", "about", "dipping", "your", "toe", "there", "into", "a", "very", "hot", "political", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "You know, I didn't because, Piers, the foundation of our faith is based out of Israel.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "because", ",", "Piers", ",", "the", "foundation", "of", "our", "faith", "is", "based", "out", "of", "Israel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Is he into this P90X thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "into", "this", "P90X", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Let's see --", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "see", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "No, he works out.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "works", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Every day?", "question_tokens": ["Every", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "No, I don't work out every day.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "work", "out", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "When people go to vote now, at the -- in November, what is the key message you would -- if you were, perhaps, Barack Obama and Mitt Romney here and you wanted them to declare things, what do you want them to declare, truthfully, to the electorate, to make a decision about them?", "question_tokens": ["When", "people", "go", "to", "vote", "now", ",", "at", "the", "--", "in", "November", ",", "what", "is", "the", "key", "message", "you", "would", "--", "if", "you", "were", ",", "perhaps", ",", "Barack", "Obama", "and", "Mitt", "Romney", "here", "and", "you", "wanted", "them", "to", "declare", "things", ",", "what", "do", "you", "want", "them", "to", "declare", ",", "truthfully", ",", "to", "the", "electorate", ",", "to", "make", "a", "decision", "about", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Well, I don't know if I can give them advice.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "can", "give", "them", "advice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Do you think it's just poison?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "just", "poison", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Well, I would love for it to, but it seems like as long as I can remember, it's always happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "love", "for", "it", "to", ",", "but", "it", "seems", "like", "as", "long", "as", "I", "can", "remember", ",", "it", "'s", "always", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Would you like it to stop?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "it", "to", "stop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Oh, I'd love it to stop.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "'d", "love", "it", "to", "stop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Are you or not -- are you not?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "or", "not", "--", "are", "you", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "That's a lot to assume.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "lot", "to", "assume", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Are you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "That's a lot to assume, brother.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "lot", "to", "assume", ",", "brother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Where do you get your facts?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "get", "your", "facts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Let me ask you a direct question.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "a", "direct", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "IN", ":", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Are you or have you ever been a liberal?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "or", "have", "you", "ever", "been", "a", "liberal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "I don't know what that -- what that is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "that", "--", "what", "that", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "How often do you agree with him about any political issue?", "question_tokens": ["How", "often", "do", "you", "agree", "with", "him", "about", "any", "political", "issue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "A lot.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "How often do you disagree with him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "often", "do", "you", "disagree", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "A lot.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Are you a conservative?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "conservative", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Yes, I'm a conservative.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "conservative", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kenny"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Would you -- would you categorize him as more of a liberal?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "--", "would", "you", "categorize", "him", "as", "more", "of", "a", "liberal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I would categorize Kenny as an independent, actually, a really --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "categorize", "Kenny", "as", "an", "independent", ",", "actually", ",", "a", "really", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Do you vote?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "vote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Do you vote?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "vote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "I think everybody should vote.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "everybody", "should", "vote", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "WP", ":", "DT", "CD", "WDT", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Who do you vote for normally?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "vote", "for", "normally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "I've always voted for the best person, what -- the one that -- that moved me, that I felt would inspire me and would inspire everything else around me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "always", "voted", "for", "the", "best", "person", ",", "what", "--", "the", "one", "that", "--", "that", "moved", "me", ",", "that", "I", "felt", "would", "inspire", "me", "and", "would", "inspire", "everything", "else", "around", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Did you vote for Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "vote", "for", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I don't think that's proper for you to even ask that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "'s", "proper", "for", "you", "to", "even", "ask", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "No, I don't -- I don't think it's proper for you to ask that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "proper", "for", "you", "to", "ask", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "I really don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers Morgan"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Why do I feel I'm losing control of this interview?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "I", "feel", "I", "'m", "losing", "control", "of", "this", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Ladies and gentlemen, Piers Morgan received a hug.", "answer_tokens": ["Ladies", "and", "gentlemen", ",", "Piers", "Morgan", "received", "a", "hug", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "My god, is that the first time anyone has hugged you in your life?", "question_tokens": ["My", "god", ",", "is", "that", "the", "first", "time", "anyone", "has", "hugged", "you", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Probably.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "You see what I'm talking about?", "question_tokens": ["You", "see", "what", "I", "'m", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "I love CNN, by the way.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "CNN", ",", "by", "the", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "CD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Harking who you actually vote for to one side, what are the issues that you really are divided over, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Harking", "who", "you", "actually", "vote", "for", "to", "one", "side", ",", "what", "are", "the", "issues", "that", "you", "really", "are", "divided", "over", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "CD", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Well, I can tell you that the issues that we hear, we -- you know, we tour like crazy, 60 some odd cities this year all over the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "that", "the", "issues", "that", "we", "hear", ",", "we", "--", "you", "know", ",", "we", "tour", "like", "crazy", ",", "60", "some", "odd", "cities", "this", "year", "all", "over", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Who do you think would do a better job with America in relation purely to jobs come the next presidential election?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "would", "do", "a", "better", "job", "with", "America", "in", "relation", "purely", "to", "jobs", "come", "the", "next", "presidential", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "I mean if you're asking me that, I think a businessman does, because a businessman creates jobs.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "if", "you", "'re", "asking", "me", "that", ",", "I", "think", "a", "businessman", "does", ",", "because", "a", "businessman", "creates", "jobs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "Kenny?", "question_tokens": ["Kenny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Well, I think that it's up to each of us.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "up", "to", "each", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Virginia"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "EX", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ":", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Well, in my home, there on our family farm, seven generations of my family has been on this -- stewarded at this farm in Virginia.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "my", "home", ",", "there", "on", "our", "family", "farm", ",", "seven", "generations", "of", "my", "family", "has", "been", "on", "this", "--", "stewarded", "at", "this", "farm", "in", "Virginia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Because I want them to understand the safety of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "want", "them", "to", "understand", "the", "safety", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "But a number of your family went to Virginia Tech, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "a", "number", "of", "your", "family", "went", "to", "Virginia", "Tech", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Virginia Tech"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Why do you hate it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "hate", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Let me explain why I hate it.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "explain", "why", "I", "hate", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 739, "question": "I mean are you going to outlaw alcohol and cars?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "are", "you", "going", "to", "outlaw", "alcohol", "and", "cars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Now see, I find that --", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "see", ",", "I", "find", "that", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "You would shoot them dead?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "shoot", "them", "dead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "But how do you think you could tighten the laws up?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "do", "you", "think", "you", "could", "tighten", "the", "laws", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "-- keep your limey Brit nose out of it.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "keep", "your", "limey", "Brit", "nose", "out", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "Is the total murder rate that different?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "total", "murder", "rate", "that", "different", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Colorado"]}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 787, "question": "What would you -- what would you suggest, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "--", "what", "would", "you", "suggest", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 788, "answer": "I think that you've got to bring in new gun laws which prohibit the purchase of assault weapons, for example; the purchase of 6,000 rounds of ammunition on the Internet, as that Colorado assassin was able to get perfectly legally.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "bring", "in", "new", "gun", "laws", "which", "prohibit", "the", "purchase", "of", "assault", "weapons", ",", "for", "example", ";", "the", "purchase", "of", "6,000", "rounds", "of", "ammunition", "on", "the", "Internet", ",", "as", "that", "Colorado", "assassin", "was", "able", "to", "get", "perfectly", "legally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 814, "question": "Do you know what a hillbilly is, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "a", "hillbilly", "is", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 815, "answer": "I know what a hillbilly is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "what", "a", "hillbilly", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 853, "question": "It was an amazing moment, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "an", "amazing", "moment", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 854, "answer": "I wanted to -- I wanted to hire his speechwriter, quite frankly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wanted", "to", "--", "I", "wanted", "to", "hire", "his", "speechwriter", ",", "quite", "frankly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 866, "question": "Is that what you want to see?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "want", "to", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 867, "answer": "I actually feel totally responsible for where he's at.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "feel", "totally", "responsible", "for", "where", "he", "'s", "at", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 907, "question": "What, 30 years?", "question_tokens": ["What", ",", "30", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 908, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]